Contact

+923008665544 (Mobile) talhamuneer.mtm@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/talha-muneer-592119144 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Machine Learning Computer Vision Spatial analytics

Languages

Urdu

English

Punjabi

Talha Muneer

Computer Scientist + Data Scientist + Data Analyst + Machine Learning Specialist + Spatial Statistician

Faisalabad District

Summary

Hello, this is talha,

I am here working as a data scientist and spatial analytics specialist. I have strength on Machine Learning, Data Mining, and Deep learning algorithms using python language, and have a grip on Geographic Information System and remote sensing techniques in the spatial analytics field.

Currently working as Research Assistant at "Spatial Analytics Research Group-(SAR)", Website: "sar.org.pk"

Experience

Freelancer

2 years 2 months

Data Scientist

November 2019 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Software Developer

November 2019 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Researcher

Data Scientist

August 2018 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Punjab, Pakistan

Brainplow

1 year 1 month

Cloud Computing

October 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Pakistan-Lahore

Cloud Computing

October 2017 - 2018 (1 year)

Lahore

Self-employed
Oracle Developer
October 2017 - November 2017 (2 months)
Pakistan

Education

National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences MS(CS), Computer Science · (2018 - 2021)

Government College University, Faisalabad Bachelor's degree, Computer Science (2013 - 2017)

Punjab Group Of College Intermediate, F.Sc (Pre-Engineering) · (2011 - 2013)